<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>

    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main5">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="open">open</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fragment">Fragment</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "A simple pendulum consists of a mass m hanging from a string of length L and fixed at a pivot point.
        When displaced to an initial angle and released, the pendulum will swing back and forth with periodic motion.
        Its time period is calculated by\n
                "T = 2π √ l/g\n
                "where T = Time Period\n
                "π = 3.147(the constant)\n
                "√ = Square root\n
                "l = length of the string\n
                "g = gravity constant\n
        "The only things that affect the period of a simple pendulum are its length and the acceleration due to gravity.
        So these are the two parameters provided below so you may change them according to your desire in order to gain the concept"
        
    </string>
    <string name="projectile">
        By definition, a projectile has a single force that acts upon it - the force of gravity.
        If there were any other force acting upon an object, then that object would not be a projectile.
        Thus, the free-body diagram of a projectile would show a single force acting downwards and labeled force of gravity.\n
        Many students have difficulty with the concept that the only force acting upon an upward moving projectile is gravity.
        Their conception of motion prompts them to think that if an object is moving upward,
        then there must be an upward force. And if an object is moving upward and rightward, there must be both an upward and rightward force.\n
        A force is only required to maintain an acceleration. And in the case of a projectile that is moving upward,
        there is a downward force and a downward acceleration. That is, the object is moving upward and slowing down.\n
        Following here is the demonstration of a projectile that how it covers its time of flight by changing
        the position of the projectile and hoe the gravity affects on it.
    </string>
    <string name="harmonic" tools:ignore="StringEscaping">
        "In mechanics and physics, simple harmonic motion is a special type of periodic motion where the restoring force on the moving object is directly proportional to the objec
        t\'s displacement magnitude and acts towards
        the object's equilibrium position. It results in an oscillation which, if uninhibited
        by friction or any other dissipation of energy, continues indefinitely.
       Simple harmonic motion can serve as a mathematical model
        for a variety of motions, but is typified by the oscillation of a mass on a spring when it is subject to
        the linear elastic restoring force given by Hooke's law. The motion is sinusoidal in time and demonstrates a single resonant frequency"
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>